

Yury Kastsen

- +48881096343
- kastenedev@gmail.com
- Wrocław

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kastsen

Website: https://mentalmerging.netlify.app/

Github: https://github.com/kastsen

Introduction

I help bring concepts to life, ensuring projects are launched on time. Experience in developing playable advertising materials, games, apps, web sites, tools, and frameworks. Automation of builds, process optimization. Effective communication with clients and team. I hope to see the world change, so I always strive to connect my work and life with progressive projects.

My technology stack includes: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Webpack, Pixi.js, Create.js, Three.js, Gatsby.js, HTML5, Pug.js, CSS3, SCSS, Bash, Git and more.

I'm now looking forward to using my skills and experience in a fulfilling position.

Experience

12/2022 - until now Web Games Developer

QS Games

Web games and tools development and maintenance service:

CORAL ISLE 2 - https://coralisle2.quartsoft.com/index.html FARLAND - https://farland.quartsoft.com/index.html PAPAYA - https://papaya.quartsoft.com/index.html

 \cdot Skills: JavaScript \cdot Typescript \cdot Webpack \cdot Pixi JS \cdot Create JS \cdot React \cdot Redux \cdot HTML5 \cdot Git \cdot mySQL \cdot REST API

03/2020 - 08/2022 Playable Ads Developer

Vizor Games

Built and maintained playable ad frameworks. Automated build and optimization processes and tasks. Participated in project team meetings and communicated effectively with customer and across other technology and creative staff.

Skills: Node.js · npm · Webpack · JavaScript · Matter JS · Bash · Pixi.js · Spine

12/2019 - 03/2020

Front-end Developer

Bamboo Apps

Project support and maintenance service. Interviews, onboarding for new employees. Skills: JavaScript \cdot Node.js \cdot Express.js \cdot mySQL \cdot CSS3 \cdot SCSS \cdot SPA \cdot UI \cdot Github \cdot Webpack \cdot Git \cdot SASS \cdot AJAX \cdot Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) \cdot npm \cdot ES6+ \cdot API \cdot Pug.js

05/2019 - 05/2020

Front-end Development Speaker

School MyFreedomIT

Skills: Public Speaking · CSS3 · HTML5 · Git · Bootstrap · JavaScript

02/2018 - 11/2019

Front-end Developer

Logic Software Inc.

Development from scratch: created ways of implementation, organized the work, created a basic full-configured version of the project. Implemented designs and logic that work across all modern desktop browsers.

Monitored the quality of solutions and code style during code reviews.

Active participation in the discussion of ways to implement tasks with the customer. Creating an application from the beginning, taking into account the most modern practices, approaches and ways of passive optimization. Team including designers, developers and marketing. June training. Support and optimization of the project.

Skills: Node.js \cdot JavaScript \cdot CSS3 \cdot SCSS \cdot React \cdot Web Design \cdot Agile Methodologies \cdot Scrum \cdot UX \cdot jQuery \cdot Webpack \cdot Git \cdot SASS \cdot AJAX \cdot JSX \cdot Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) \cdot JSON \cdot npm \cdot Yarn \cdot ES6+ \cdot API \cdot PHP \cdot mySQL

06/2015 - 12/2017

Web Development Specialist

inAweb

Web sites design, development and support. Building custom WordPress themes and plugins. HTML-markup, PHP, MySQL, jQuery.

05/2011 - 08/2015

Content Manager

Cultutal Daily News Portal

Content management, digital marketing, planning and implementation of audience engagement activities, generation of new ideas, community management.

Knowledge and skills

Languages:

Byelorussian (proficient) Russian (proficient) English (intermediate) Polish (pre-intermediate) Czech (pre-intermediate)

Skills:

HTML5 CSS3 SASS npm PixiJS WebGL JavaScript webpack node.js GatsbyJS ReactJS **React Native** Web Games Three.js Project planning MySQL OOP Team management Bash Redux Agile methodologies

Education

Level of education

University

Erasmus+ EVS
Politologie

BSPU
Philology. Literature. Journalism

Certificates and trainings

2019 **School MyfreedomIT** Javascript, React JS. Front-end Development

2013 Používání vizuálních symbolů a tvůrčích přístupů

Prague

Známost s českou zkušeností v použití vizuálních symbolů a kreativních

přístupů k sociální činnosti.

Interests and hobbies

Music Nature Quad roller skating